Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1948-1988 (Box OV 1-OV 15)
  - Client File (Box OV 1)
    - Grossman, Suzanne (Box OV 5)
      - Chemin de Fer
        - Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles, Calif.
          - Miscellany
            - Poster, 1969 (Container 244)
      - There's One in Every Marriage
        - Foreign productions
          - Australia
            - Photographs, 1972 (Container 250)
    - Hagen, Uta
      - Charlotte
        - Contracts and correspondence
          - Floor plans and elevations for Smith Theater 14, Northampton, Mass., 1970 (Container 255)
        - Miscellany (Box OV 6)
        - Photographs, undated (Container 260)
      - Saint Joan
        - Photograph, undated (Container 265)
    - Hansberry, Lorraine (Box OV 7)
      - Miscellany
        - Poster for The Sign in Sidney Brustein's Window, undated (Container 271)
    - Hayes, Helen
      - Films and plays
        - APA Repertory Company
          - Printed matter
            - Miscellany
              - Poster for The Show-Off, undated (Container 281)
        - Shakespeare Revisited: A Program for Two Players
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, 1962 (Container 286)
      - Television
        - “Helen Hayes, Portrait of an American Actress”
          - Printed matter
            - Poster and sketch, undated (Container 299)
    - Jones, James Earl
      - The End of the Road
        - Miscellany
          - Poster, 1970 (Container 344)
      - King Oedipus
        - Handbill, undated (Container 359)
    - Kesselman, Wendy
      - Becca
        - Poster, undated (Container 422)
      - Maggie Magalita
        - Printed matter
          - Poster, 1980 (Container 423)
      - My Sister in This House
        - Foreign rights and productions
          - Yugoslavia
            - Poster, 1981-1982 (Container 425)
    - Kilroy, Thomas
      - The Death and Resurrection of Mr. Roche
        - Printed matter
          - Poster, undated (Container 428)
    - Kübler-Ross, Elisabeth (Box OV 8)
      - Working It Through
        - Photograph, 1981 (Container 440)
    - Lampell, Millard
      - The Wall (two-act play)
        - Foreign rights and productions
          - Sweden
            - Poster, 1963 (Container 448)
    - Latouche, John, and Jerome Moross (Box OV 9)
      - Ballet Ballads
        - Music Box Theatre, New York, N.Y.
          - Photographs
            - Contact sheet, 1948 (Container 458)
      - The Golden Apple
        - Miscellany
          - Photograph, undated (Container 460)
        - Phoenix Theatre, New York, N.Y.
          - Photographs, undated (Container 460)
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, 1953-1954 (Container 460)
    - Letton, Francis and Jennette Dowling (Box OV 10)
      - The Young Elizabeth
        - Play
          - British productions
            - Printed matter
              - Poster, undated (Container 477)
    - Levine, Rhoda
      - Typescripts
        - Examples of typefaces, undated (Container 480)
    - Linney, Romulus
      - The Sorrows of Frederick
        - Center Theatre Group, Los Angeles, Calif.
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, 1967 (Container 494)
    - Locke, Samuel
      - The Woman with Red Hair
        - Correspondence
          - Poster, undated (Container 503)
    - Margolin, Janet
      - David and Lisa
        - Printed matter
          - Promotional brochure, 1962 (Container 512)
    - Petrie, Daniel
      - Morning Sun
        - Printed matter
          - Poster, undated (Container 553)
    - Riggs, Lynn (Box OV 11)
      - Toward the Western Sky
        - Photographs, 1951 (Container 574)
    - Roberts, John (Box OV 12)
      - In the Matter of J. Robert Oppenheimer
        - Center Theatre Group, Mark Taper Forum, Los Angeles, Calif.
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, 1968 (Container 580)
        - Repertory Theater of Lincoln Center, New York, N.Y.
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, 1969 (Container 583)
    - Sackler, Howard
      - The Great White Hope
        - Productions
          - Broadway
            - Miscellany
              - Poster, undated (Container 604)
              - New York Drama Critics' Circle Award for Best Play, 1968-1969 (Container 604)
    - Sandburg, Carl
      - The Greatest Story Ever Told
        - Photograph, undated (Container 615)
      - Miscellany
        - Photograph, undated (Container 617)
      - Sandburg's Lincoln (Box OV 13)
        - Photograph, undated (Container 627)
    - Shange, Ntozake
      - Creation for Liberation
        - Poster, 1988 (Container 649)
    - Spock, Benjamin
      - National Broadcasting System ratings sheet, 1955-1956 (Container 661)
    - Stanley, Kim (Box OV 14)
      - The Chase
        - Photograph, undated (Container 662)
      - Miscellany
        - Photographs, undated (Container 669)
      - Natural Affection
        - Photographs, undated (Container 669)
      - Seance on a Wet Afternoon (Box OV 15)
        - Printed matter
          - Promotional material, undated (Container 671)
    - Stavis, Barrie
      - Lamp at Midnight
        - “Hallmark Hall of Fame”
          - Printed matter
            - Poster, undated (Container 675)
      - Miscellany
        - Poster, undated (Container 676)
    - Thurber, James
      - Music
        - Scores for The 13 Clocks and A Thurber Carnival, 1952, 1960 (Container 685)
    - Vaughn, Stuart
      - Miscellany
        - Printed matter
          - Poster for Abe Lincoln in Illinois, undated (Container 692)
      - Seattle Repertory Theatre, Seattle, Wash.
        - Printed matter
          - Poster, 1963-1964 (Container 694)
    - Weaver, Fritz
      - All American
        - Poster, undated (Container 706)
      - Lorenzo
        - Poster, undated (Container 714)